so i've been told many times so far that
it looks like
i live in my mom's attic over here
um and that is absolutely 100 true and
so
to kind of kick off the spirit of
that excitement of living with your
parents um
in their attic and how joyful that is uh
let's start a lives in
mom's house gang hashtag branded
um that's the new gang of the channel
all right guys
so because i am actually living in the
attic of my mom's house and not the
basement
that gives me much more say in um and
knowledge than everyone else who lives
in their mom's basement
and also just lives in their own house
because i'm actually living
in the absolute highest point over
everyone else and because i'm higher up
than everyone else that gives me much
more power and
assertiveness and dominance over your
opinions
so listen up you're about to learn
something very very smart
today we're looking at a small account
growth uh strata what do we
we're trying to grow a small account as
quickly as possible let's do it
[Music]
so as many of you guys already know i am
growing a
massive account i am growing a 100 000
account currently right now
it started beginning of september going
very well so far
making some good money on the first two
episodes there uh about
10 actually so please check that out in
the wherever on the side
uh and you can watch to see how i'm
actually trading a a big big account
a little bit safer than normal uh but i
wanted to come across at you guys with a
small account so that you guys can learn
uh how you would you would probably go
about it uh and i just wanted to make a
couple adjustments
to maybe my own trading strategy
something that would be more
uh useful for somebody who was just
really trying to i know the emotional
side's there for you guys you're really
trying to
push it as quick as possible and grow
that account as quick as possible
even though i said don't do it don't try
to grow your count that quickly
uh you're gonna lose but we want to
adapt here we want to make sure that
you guys are doing the the terrible
terrible dopamine addiction things that
you need
to fix your mind
[Laughter]
anyways there's going to be small
adjustments on
little bits of my strategy that's going
to be a little bit better for you guys
to grow your small account
and then so if you guys do want to
subscribe i will be using
this strategy in the new year to grow a
small account after i'm done this big
100k flip account challenge to see how
big i can get that one because i only
want to do one at a time guys
come on i'm not mamba effects here he
can do two challenges at once
shout out to mamba that guy is a
freaking beast
i don't know how he does two at once
that's crazy all right enough about
other people's channel let's talk about
me this is my channel talk about me um
the strategy that i really needed to
dive into here
is going to be focused on getting you as
many trades as possible
and trading in high volume times so the
london and the new york session uh
you're gonna be able to trade as much as
possible with my personal strategy
i'm basically only trading on the new
york open so we're gonna try to adapt it
to be
much more versatile so that you can use
at any point during the day except for
the asia session because that is just a
huge old waste of time
and it's going to be much more fast
paced it's going to be a scalping-ish
strategy
uh so you're not going to be holding
things for very long you're
hopefully going to be holding things uh
briefly and then you're getting in and
out as quick
as possible you're trying to flip for a
good risk reward
and that's all it is it's going to be
maybe
two to three r trades and you're gonna
get in and out and you're gonna go to
the next trade next trade next trade and
then each and every day
you're gonna be able to look for the
next setups and hopefully
uh you can go from there now the thing i
wanted to focus on is we're only gonna
be using the new york uh
sorry the uh the us dollar pairs uh just
because it's gonna be a little bit
easier for you guys to track
because i'm assuming it's going to be
mostly beginners using a strategy with a
small account
um we don't want to uh cloud ourselves
with these cross pairs and these smaller
pairs
that don't have as much authority over
the market so we're only going to look
at these
dolls us dollar pairs if you don't see a
setup you don't trade for the day
listen to me let's do it all right guys
i'm going to try to break this down as
simple as freaking possible number one
we're going to start on the higher time
frame we're going to look at the one
hour the one hour
is going to be a well balanced area
where we can look at the
overall bigger trend of the week
and of the day so that you can kind of
know what trend you're going to be
following
now you're going to follow the trend no
matter what
unless you see something
very very simple going on like this so
we see
a downtrend here and we see a
significant low being made right
and then we're coming back we're pulling
back we're showing weakness in the
market
right we're really pulling back to these
previous areas that brought us down
there right
and that's kind of the thing that's
showing us weakness so we're kind of
consolidating
we're not just coming back halfway and
then continuing back down
if you know what i mean so if this one's
continuing up we see a low here
come back halfway and then continuing up
we're not showing any weakness in that
movement right there right
that makes sense to you guys hopefully
now here we're showing a lot of weakness
in that area right
so now what we're seeing is we're seeing
a move
past that level and then it's reversing
back in this is going to be the only
case and i'm just going to try to make
it very simple we're not going to go
into huge huge
uh technicals around this and we're not
going to dive into massive explanations
of the logic behind my strategy
in depth if you guys are interested in
very very detailed stuff
you guys will have to contact me and
then we can work on it
on things together on like a one-on-one
session or something like this
but once you see kind of that brief
little wicks past a
move or our pivot low after it's shown
weakness
this is really just telling us that that
was a stop hunt essentially
showing that the market makers that we
can then move it up in the other
direction here
so another example quickly you can see a
bunch of lows
here right and the more lows the more
important it is
so now we see on the euro that there's
just little bits of moves just past that
so this is the only situation that i
want you guys to completely
not trade um and say there's not a
chance that i will take that trade
because what we're seeing right now is
we want to follow the trend like i said
but we're seeing possible chances of a
massive reversal here and you can see
that here and you can see that here
now where else does that happen you can
kind of see it
a previous supply area here
where that's not a great great example
but you're seeing the wicks and then
it's coming back down with a lot of
momentum in the other direction
another example we're wicking above
something and then coming back in that
direction
and we're closing back within hopefully
this is kind of obvious to you guys
you're gonna have to play around with it
a little bit and now
this is kind of a good example in the
opposite side
where we're actually seeing it into our
favor uh because this
is i would say arguably an uptrend here
all right you're coming up here and then
you're seeing these lows and then it's
actually wicking in the direction that
you want
so that makes sense to you guys here
right we're in an uptrend
and we've just faked to the downside and
now we're seeing
a direction in the uptrend uh in the
actual direction that we want to
continue in
so that's actually going to make it even
more likely for you guys but don't
consider that too too much because we're
not going to be trying to bet more
uh just because we see added proof
in this particular strategy uh and
that's that's up for something
a little bit more complicated where we
want to add risk and we don't really
want to do that in
somewhat of a beginner strategy here now
the next thing that you guys are going
to want to do
here is if you're looking at the london
session
the thing to know about the london
session is it often picks the trend of
the day
so the new york session will often
follow this is quite obvious
when you look at the past you see london
session here by the way guys
if you want this london session new york
session i have a bunch of indicators
here i don't use them
i just only have my sessions london new
york asia that's this one and then i
have monday's range that tells me what
day monday
is that's all the indicators i use you
guys can use those too
so if you guys want to know the sessions
there throw those up on your chart
and that's going to help you a lot but a
lot of the time you're going to see
this is kind of the structure of it you
go into the trend of the day
we're not seeing any like major
manipulation or anything so it's just a
nice smooth
and then we start pulling back for the
new york open right
and then we see some significant
movement that's going to be very very
common
in most of the days that you see or
you see something like you see the
london opening up
it seems like there's a significant move
there and it starts pulling back from
new york and then new york continues
so sorry continues that trend right
there
right and that's basically what we're
going to be looking for
most of the time now if you're trying to
trade in the
london session you're not going to be
able to know what trend it is for the
most of the day right so what you're
going to have to do is hopefully follow
the higher time frame trend
so what we're going to then look for is
a pullback
for any significant day
to any sort of important
untested level right that's an untested
level here
and notice that we're also we're kind of
going just
beyond these lows because that's kind of
where a lot of people stops might be
right so this is kind of good indication
right uh you're gonna have to use a
little bit of your own judgment here
because i can't go into super super
detail
right in a small video like this but if
you guys want some more info on things
like this please jump into the streams
i can explain things a lot better in
stream with a much more time
than a quick 10 minute video here for
you guys and honestly you know you guys
don't have 10 minutes to watch like a
strategy that's just be giving to you
guys
you should uh you might not be doing
super super well in uh forex uh
very very soon because i guarantee uh
this is some of the best
best content that you're gonna learn so
then what we're gonna be looking for
is a rejection off of a previous level
and we're going to be bouncing off with
significance right
so it's going to be very very
generalized here and this is not
a great example where i can say
anything obvious here but you see it
bounces off of it
and then you see significance that's
really all i can unfortunately say about
this perfect example
of it bouncing off of it but there's a
couple things that kind of line up
the one that you're gonna be looking for
is bouncing off of a
supplier demand zone some sort of level
of importance another one is looking for
sweeps below levels so stopping people
out of their orders
and the third one is breaking levels
to the upside now you don't see any
levels being broken here
until you get way up here right if that
makes sense because the previous green
candle
is the previous level there wasn't
actually really any levels there right
so what we're going to do is we're going
to follow that on the five minute and
once we see the significance
then you're gonna jump in on the trade
and you're gonna put your stop
below those lows and then you're gonna
follow that trend to the next
major level of importance and now if you
guys obviously can't find levels of
importance
this is not where this video is going to
help you out but there are other videos
i have that can teach you
significant levels of importance
basically it's going to be breaking down
how we're going to be trading the
london open so you're going to leave
that to run
hopefully into the new york open if you
see
something on the new york open that
shows
a previous important level something
that we've just actually targeted that's
why we targeted a previous important
level
and then you see a significant pullback
and just wicking above you looking at
the higher time frame you can see
the level just barely being broken up
it's still closing above so i'm not i'm
not too too concerned about this level
uh being faked out but if you're seeing
these wicks on the higher time
frame and then the reversal being hard
then we're going to want to get out of
that trade as quick as possible
and then we're going to want to be
looking for an actual short on the new
york open
but if we don't see those wicks above
then what we're going to be looking for
is we're going to be looking for a
continuation
some sort of pullback and the exact same
sort of thing again
continuing in to the same way that we
just deal with
the london session so we can see okay a
significant level was here
right and then we bounced off of that
one and we started
if we started rallying right off of that
so you could have entered up here
and then you might have gotten stopped
at a break even after we got into a
little bit of profit
uh but that's completely up to you so
let's just kind of look at another
another day here essentially what we're
going to be doing with the strategy is
we're going to be taking two trades a
day
uh on any one of the or two possible
trades a day on all of the
um us dollar pairs and you're gonna be
able to scan through them all
and look at them all individually right
so let's look
at this next day here using the euro
dollar here
right so what we wanted to do is we had
the upper
time frame is on an uptrend so
here we see okay it's actually coming
into the reverse direction
um we can look for a little bit for a
little bit of pullback for maybe a
bounce off of a significant level
so a significant level to me might have
been this one because it's kind of
untested
so this might be a little bit hard for
you to see
of any major significant levels but it
could have been that one
and then we see the reversal happening
right around
right around um here right
and then you can look for an entry and
then rally up
to previous highs now mind you we didn't
actually get into any previous highs
and what we did see is actually
what i just explained that you don't
want to see here is just the
the brief little wicks above on the new
york open
and then closes back below this is
showing signs
of a reversal on the new york open
because this is very common for the new
york
session to do if it doesn't continue and
that's where we would just cut the trade
completely short
and again you've just made another trade
and what you can do
if you are so eager is look for a short
now using that exact same method
looking for some sort of pullback and
then continuation into the trend
and then targeting significant lows
on the previous day right so right about
here would be a significant low
hopefully that makes a lot of sense for
you guys and again if you guys are a
little bit confused make sure you jump
and watch the streams i
i stream most weekdays some days i do
have to take off
but i try my best to teach as well as i
can and answer as many questions as
possible
absolutely free of charge for you if you
guys do uh want to learn on one-on-one
mentoring then that is completely up to
you
but that is not uh included in the
streams so let's just look at another
random day back here maybe
so let's see okay this is a downtrend
previous days are a downtrend
what we can see is on the london open
it did actually start breaking down and
what we would want to look for is a
rejection off of
some sort of level like this a sub uh
important level because it completely
plummeted
right we're not going to be able to get
in right away we want to look for a
rejection off of here
but it didn't really give us a great
rejection off of that kind of wicked and
then just didn't do anything
so it came up again and it completely
faked out some people and stopped some
people out
this is again again another sign that's
actually going to continue down
so once we see that fake out and we want
to continue that trend because we always
want to continue the trends remember
that's the most important thing
then we can start targeting and i'm not
going to say that we just hit that
perfectly
let's say that we hit the previous lows
as a best case uh best case we hit 3
3 4r um looking back here
maybe you were targeting
the actually you might have been
targeting these lows here you might have
actually hit it perfectly here
um it's just a little bit odd we don't
know exactly where we're gonna be
hitting but i'm just trying to give you
kind of a rough idea of what was going
to happen here
and then what do we see let's say you
took some profits let's say you've moved
your stop forward
and now we see okay this was a
significant low
right and significant lows here and now
it's really rallying off of it so we
would just exit that right away
and we look for a long on a reversal
right so that would be your second trade
of the day
let's look for another trade here
in a downtrend this is the previous day
in a downtrend it fakes it to the upside
right we don't want to be we don't want
to be going long
and then we see a rejection
off of let's just draw this on the 15
minute there might be an important level
here
okay we actually see the sweeps above
and you can see on the 15 minute how
it's just perfectly sweeping above that
asia high and then we're breaking down
and we can then place our stop above
here
and where would we target probably these
lows right there
so you can see each day you're usually
getting out of your trade
quite quickly by the next session right
so in the new york session here you
probably didn't want to trade because it
just looked like a big
big old piece of piece of burning fire i
don't know
it just looked like a dumpster fire
didn't it you don't really know what to
do there
so let's just look once again if you
guys are curious
let's look at this one kind of looks
kind of cool to me
uh so this is a i would say that this is
a downtrend on the higher time frame of
course of course
what we're seeing is the london session
going to the downside then we're looking
for some sort of significant rejection
that could have been a rejection off of
that you might have jumped in a little
bit early here
and then gotten stopped out there to be
fair you might have gotten stopped out
right here
but then you see again it comes back up
goes up to the previous day's high
and this barely tops it and then starts
breaking down now once again
you see the breakdown let's say you
jumped in a little bit late over here
and we targeted the previous day's lows
right there you go and you would have
covered your
previous day's lows you might have even
got a little bit farther there
you would have covered your loss
completely perfect
let's just look at maybe another one
here why not
london session we see a little bit fake
out to the upside
maybe you completely missed this you
might have gotten in here
uh but you want to continue that trend
of course we would have waited because
it would have taken too long here to get
us in
and we would have waited for a pullback
here you would have completely missed it
i think
and the new york doesn't really look
like anything to me either
once again this was a uptrend we were
looking at an uptrend but this time
we see a bounce off of here i don't know
if this is anything significant it could
have been you could have gotten stopped
out of break even
after it started rounding up a little
bit uh when it came back down here
uh but you can see after it did break
out you do see that wicking action there
and we would have closed it immediately
no matter what anyways and then we would
have completely gone short
as quick as possible and we would have
been targeting
the previous day's lows perfectly
that's all you would have been doing all
right guys hopefully that was a super
simple strategy it might be a little bit
confusing please watch the video again
uh send it around uh see if some people
can kind of help you
because it's very similar to a lot of
stuff i do normally trade
just to be a little bit more fast paced
and you're going to be able to place a
lot more trades
and hopefully grow your account really
really quickly and now the thing is
when you are trading like this i do
still recommend that you are
risking a very small amount of your
capital size so i do have videos on how
to actually manage your risk properly so
please make sure you
hit some of those other videos there you
can watch those in detail and if you do
want to learn
a bunch more uh again watch the streams
and you will learn a ton there's also if
you guys are interested
uh discord in the link in the
description and
you guys can actually ask some questions
talk to some people live throughout the
day
and there's also a signal group if you
want to join in that as well
see you guys next time